<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SpikeKit on Spike</title><link>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/</link><description>Recent content in SpikeKit on Spike</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cron Plugin</title><link>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/cron-plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/cron-plugin/</guid><description>Cron Plugins execute code on an interval.
To start developing a SpikeKit Cron Plugin Fork this repository to create your own working copy. Copy /src/plugins/blueprintCronPlugin and rename the folder to something unique. Edit main.js and add supplementary files as required. Submit a Pull Request with your plugin. Spike Collaborators will review your plugin and suggest any required changes. Once approved, your plugin will go live with the next update of Spike.</description></item><item><title>Logging</title><link>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/logging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/logging/</guid><description>Logging with SpikeKit is powered by Winston. This allows us to selectively log things that happen and better respond to errors in Spike. Do not use console.log or console.error to log messages. Instead, use one of the log levels below with the SpikeKit logger.
Log Levels Log levels in SpikeKit go along with npm convention. Here are the log levels we use, in order of highest to lowest priority:
Level Function Call Meaning Error spikeKit.</description></item><item><title>Standard Plugin</title><link>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/standard-plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/spikekit/standard-plugin/</guid><description>Standard Plugins accept and act upon commands given with the bot&amp;rsquo;s prefix.
To start developing a SpikeKit Standard Plugin Fork this repository to create your own working copy. Copy /src/plugins/blueprintPlugin and rename the folder to something unique. Edit main.js and add supplementary files as required. Submit a Pull Request with your plugin. Spike Collaborators will review your plugin and suggest any required changes. Once approved, your plugin will go live with the next update of Spike.</description></item></channel></rss>