<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contributing on Spike</title><link>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/</link><description>Recent content in Contributing on Spike</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bug Reports</title><link>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/bug-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/bug-reports/</guid><description>So, you&amp;rsquo;ve found a bug in Spike and want to report it, eh? It&amp;rsquo;s a fairly simple endeavor, but please be sure to follow instructions carefully so we get all the information we need to reproduce and fix the bug!
To submit a Bug Report, visit this link, or file a new issue and select &amp;ldquo;Bug Report&amp;rdquo; from the menu. You&amp;rsquo;ll be presented with a template containing a few important questions to answer.</description></item><item><title>Feature Requests</title><link>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/feature-requests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/feature-requests/</guid><description>So, you want a new feature in Spike, eh? It&amp;rsquo;s a fairly simple endeavor, but please be sure to follow instructions carefully so we get all the information we need to develop this feature!
To submit a Bug Report, visit this link, or file a new issue and select &amp;ldquo;Feature Request&amp;rdquo; from the menu. You&amp;rsquo;ll be presented with a template containing a few important questions to answer.
&amp;lt;!-- Thanks for taking the time to request a feature!</description></item><item><title>Project Board</title><link>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/project-board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/project-board/</guid><description>We use a Kanban-style project board to keep organized with feature and bug requests, as well as outstanding pull requests for code changes. As you follow your issue (you did file an issue for a bug report or feature request, right?) or PR, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice it head through several columns in the board. Here&amp;rsquo;s what they mean.
Collaborators: Note that Issues are not automatically progressed through the board. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to do that manually.</description></item><item><title>Submitting a Pull Request</title><link>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/submitting-a-pull-request/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://spike-2.github.io/docs/contributing/submitting-a-pull-request/</guid><description>So, you want to add a new feature in Spike, eh? It&amp;rsquo;s a fairly simple endeavor, but please be sure to follow instructions carefully so we get all the information we need to approve this feature!
Before You Begin Work on an Existing Issue Please make sure that an Issue is in the Accepted/To-Do state before beginning work on it. You can check by looking at the Projects section of the sidebar for where it is on the Roadmap.</description></item></channel></rss>